Brian Yoon

<u>byoonweb3@gmail.com</u> www.linkedin.com/in/brian-yoon-gm // https://github.com/thinkaboutmovies

Highlight

Full-stack web developer who loves NFT's and web3 technologies. My experience exploring the web3 landscape guides me in everything that I do: making decisions in fast-paced development environments and tunneling down on high priority problems in ambiguous situations. I am self-taught on all things web3 which has trained me to always be learning, keep pushing out of my intellectual comfort zone, and constantly reach out to other collectors for data analysis. Some of my favorite NFT/Crypto people include Richerd.eth, DCLBlogger, The DeFi Edge, and OxBender. My favorite NFT projects include The Metakey, Creature World, RTFKT Studios, Treeverse, Veefriends, Azukis, and Doodles.

SKILLS

Javascript, React.js, Etherscan API, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Manifold Studio, Smart Contract Deployment, Web3, Metamask, Uniswap, 1inch, Matcha, Sushiswap, NFTs, Opensea, Superrare, Rarible, Foundation, Quantum, Fractional, DAOs, Juicebox, Constitution DAO, TreasureDAO, Anchor, Slack, Zoom, Discord

PROJECTS

- Rotating Art Gallery Dynamically view your NFTs like a rotating art gallery by entering your wallet address or Opensea account name; technologies used include React.js, Modulenft API, Framer Motion, Alice Carousel. CSS Grid, and Flexbox.
- Pomodoro App Create study intervals and break times to increase productivity for longer periods of time; technologies used include React.js, Flexbox, Mongoose, Express, Node.js, and Cors.
- Coin Pouch Search for the Ether balance of NFT influencers from a search menu and check for gas; technologies used include React.js, Etherscan API, and CSS Grids.
- **Dinosaur Pets** Rest, feed, and play with your very own pet dinosaur; technologies used include Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS, Flexbox, and Bootstrap.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Community Ambassador, The Metakey, October 2021 - Present

- Advocate community ideas about partnership integrations back to the main office team
- Inform the community on the latest developments from the main office team
- Onboard new NFT holders on everything the Metakey has to offer
- Resolve the concerns of 14,723 Community Members in the Metakey Discord

Crew Member, Marugame Udon, August 2021 - December 2021

- Provided quality guest service while articulating food integrity to each Marugame Udon guest
- Operated many work stations including seimen, tempura, yusen, musubi, dishes, and cash register.
- Worked as a team player to fill in at understaffed stations while working at my own station

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY, Software Engineering Immersive, January 2022 - April 2022

 12-week intensive course that builds fluency in full-stack web development with an emphasis on a work-ready skill set.

Crypto Mindset Course, Certificate of Completion, June 2021 - July 2021

- Use Defi and Cefi applications to transfer, exchange, and stake tokens from multiple chains
- Aggregated the best resources to learn tokenomics of different chains like Luna/Phantom/Solana

Santa Monica College, 2019, A.A. Economics - In Progress